degreeplus.net 2014-12-21

# Privacy Policy - DegreePlus.net

This privacy policy was last updated on February 22nd, 2013

Degreeplus.net is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our Website, so we want you to know what information we collect and how we use that information. We reserve the right to append or otherwise modify this Privacy Statement at any time, so please re-visit this page occasionally to check for updates.

We collect various types of information from our visitors so we can adjust our site to meet our users' needs and expectations. Some of this information is collected automatically through cookies and other information is collected when you register for any of our online services or when you request information from one of our partners.

Cookies are data created by a Web server that is stored on a user's computer. It provides a way for the Website to keep track of a user's patterns and preferences and, with the cooperation of the Web browser, to store them on the user's own hard disk.

You can opt out of the use of cookies by having your browser disable cookies or warn you before accepting a cookie. Look for the cookie options in your browser in the Options or Preferences menu. 

The types of information your browser or Internet session automatically sends us each time you visit one of our sites, which we automatically collect, includes:

  * Your browser, e.g., Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator.
  * Your Internet domain, e.g., AOL, Netcom, Earthlink, etc.
  * You computer's operating system, e.g., Windows, Macintosh, UNIX, Linux.
  * Your navigation path, i.e., the URLs of where you come to our site from, which of our pages you visit, and where you go as you leave.
  * Your IP address. This is the address of a computer attached to a TCP/IP network. Every client and server station must have a unique IP address. Client workstations have either a permanent address or one that is dynamically assigned for each dial-up session. IP addresses are written as four sets of numbers separated by periods; for example, 123.123.12.1.

This information lets us see how users are finding our sites, and it tells us which pages are visited the most often so we can make our Websites more useful. 

In addition to the information automatically collected by your browser, we also collect information that you provide to us when you request information about a particular school or educational program.

Our website provides users the opportunity to request information from schools, and to learn about various education opportunities. These information request sites require users to provide contact information (name, address, phone number, email address, gender, age, work experience, etc.) as well as information about their interest in one of our educational partners (universities, colleges, test prep companies, etc.) We provide the contact information that you provide to the educational partner that you request information from. Customer interest information is collected to determine what information the customer wishes to be sent.

We use the information we automatically collect to help us better plan our Website to meet your Internet needs. Information you provide to us is used for marketing purposes, and may result in follow-up communications.

DegreePlus.net may share personally identifiable information with third party businesses for the purpose of direct marketing, telemarketing and specifically email marketing. All third parties are bound by the CAN SPAM Act (s.877) of 2003, and are required to be in full compliance of all consumer opt-out rules and regulations.

The company respects the privacy of users visiting our sites and will abide by all applicable laws concerning the release of personal information. If you do not want to receive our e-mail marketing, please submit a request to have your e-mail address removed by clicking the "Unsubscribe" link in the email that brought you to our site.

Other than directory information, data you provide to us as you use the Website will be held in strict confidence by the company and will be used for company purposes only.

Our Websites have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
